Hello friends, Nifty is at the top and
hopefully you guys will be in good profit,
so tell the people who are on this channel
that on which question you are told the best level, the
best top card is okay and you
can see here on this channel you
go in many short videos, this streaming and
video was made in which the hidden Sanghchalak has been made, the
camera looks good on which he likes
bikes and Harihar
is represented by a good store so that you
can earn good stock permission, in that literature you are
told the juice strategy, in that long video it is
told that this is how you have to
invest in stocks, how everything is fine, then by making
this but by making a food bill you will definitely keep the channel
clean, so let's see on your face,
hence you can buy the packing problem,
one stock of the insurance sector is
coming down, there
is a reference of the long channel sector from ICE, here you
can see at 1.2, in which there has been a
great, it was 100, but today there has been a crore
gym in it and give the price here,
how much has been the delivery  70% of the total time has it been?
It will last for almost 20
minutes. The trade is for about 20 minutes. In the same period, 2006
people and 77 people have
answered this question.
We can like this page. We can
buy on the strength of
ICICI Lombard. Okay, they are
representing the entire chart. And
this can increase vitamin D.
Where is the 19th? It is
very important to know where the top is. 600, 800, make it between
1058. So how will it be able to buy on the way? I will
give you two labels. Check both of them first. Let's see what
kind of
solution we see there. Only then will we talk about the
country. We should not buy at home and do it
repeatedly. The market is all over the back.
Any customer is under any pressure, even
if the market
feels good sometimes even at a specific stop up to the navel, then it can cause
you harm. That's
quick.  There is a need to rise, if the
market is in profit for you then
why take the risk and get your profit
animated by it, okay then this should
not happen but this stock is good,
if it comes to a good level and supports then you
can bike and you will definitely
see profit, so you should invest in this type of stock,
not such small
stocks, if it falls from the top then
if it tries to climb up again, while
climbing it the reference never becomes chapter, then
you do not know that you should
not touch anything in this way, so
if you want to bike it, wash it,
we cannot track the previous 100 phases, which
bike can sink, if
this is the case then the 1450mah stock can be seen and it can be seen
from the verified support and by going through the
mixture someone comes here, then in
such a situation percentage is needed, you should
try to take all this, so
near this highest, hey next, at
which level will we talk about Tata Consumer Products, we will make a chart,
we will also see the NSC site  Let's see
again your stroke in
it, it is giving almost points the next day, if there is a
super sonic cross, then if there is a
fall in the stock from a very high, and you
can see here the posting is above lakh,
total trade buy in it and fifty one percent
people have deposited it with their hands, so let's
go and see it on the stock chart,
we can like this, this
is the reference of the stocks of the film Shuddhi sector, let's
see its volume in the graph, it has
covered light and how much profit you have kept
in the mixture, you
can see here, this is its
listing in 2012, then Asian Institute, its
stock, so today click on 10, from
here you can see that it has made so much money
that it has made you so much money,
long term and long term, I have not seen it for a
long time, that is why I always say that if
you get any opportunity
in any good stock, then buy them at the bottom,
in the recently added your
fortune had almost fallen from its top, that is why I
said
that you  Those who want to invest in this for the long term,
you can take it up, so just
see where it is, you have to invest
your entire money, not just by dividing it by half,
and you have also invested your entire money before this opportunity,
you have to invest according to your serial status, and
friend Mixi Anju Sapna Investment will be
in Ruchi Stock and Minister will be in Small Cap
and Mid Cap, so you will have to invest by diversifying in this way,
and very
soon a video will be made on this,
and now when this system season is
over, give it an injection to everyone,
I will also enjoy a little, after this I am going to
make a very beautiful video, it will be of only 2-3 series,
and how can we say TV, stock, all this
is complete, a pinch of a bunch will come, the
whole long-term recipe will come on these western,
okay, you share it,
this entire video is going to come very soon, okay, so
I have shown it to you here, so you would like to see
that the problems have been divided and placed
on the chart,
see here, Vande  When I did the entire chapter from the center
and this soil and haunted
movie tree video can be seen
at 28, human electronics,
do this thing, where has it made a recent top at 108,
it had made a straight top, it is eight, to
like it, right now the karma
money is visible here, one angle solution,
so you can definitely bike some quantity eight,
you can also say that it is
running on the internet, so see Monday, temple, if it goes up a
little and during the day,
you can bike it yourself,
if it comes down, there is support, then
retail pack internet can do one for the first week,
okay, after that, if
this stock breaks the level tomorrow, then you will take this
support below, I will take one as per the question,
dowry, okay, which is around what we are looking for, so I
hope you guys took
note, so let's go next, okay, another
very rising star of the fancy sector, that is
another thing, consumer product,
okay, there has been a lot of ignoring in it,
point note three questions, cigarettes
It's personal. If you look here, there are
1747 personal. In that, the torn notes of this
product are 6000. So look at the chart and
I can like this.
We can see some volume of consumers. It is
possible to change the blood pressure as much as I can. I will do it as
quickly as possible.
Market question. You can see here that they are
above the saffron and there is about 50 ups and
downs because this is not a plate.
Okay, and you can see that,
leave the phase in the middle and different. And here you
can see that the request is not that special. The
accused is fine. And the accused is also right,
it is a standard accused rogfp1.
So look here, you can like this album. So let's
see where this block is at the top.
So where did you make it? Why did it make it?
This is pressing from 2018.
And this is also showing an organic concentration like Tata Consumer.
So a support
enhancement, it is around 2011. So some quantity
you must have.  Bike, that is why it breaks the level of the place, that is,
due to some pressure, so from where can you get it
from the virus, you want a job, the next one which becomes successful, its level is
around 970,
if the ticket was around 90, it breaks their level and
along with this, I always say in this entire chart that it will reach
maximum fennel 125, Raja Citizen,
this clay pot country and the one which is of 1972,
its eggs will be near the year, if you had come after
drinking its support, then let's go to the next,
you can see from the figure that
today there has been a lot of buy on Don, I will
show you here, before that, let's see, the
price in it is why Singh - 06
closing why don't, 1000% exit has been done in it,
so look here, now you have been
looted and due to the atrocities,
people have deposited their hold on it by bike,
so look at the chart, you
can do central measures, let's quickly
look at the components of the dower, one is the film CG
sector stocks, this is very  Great
stock reference and here you can see
Market Commission Juan Laixeji More in
that box about hi 518 non for
its GPS six and current price phase so
update that Indian space is stuck in space you
can see these stocks and fog
good good different points 1720
Aarushi tube I always say that you must watch
long term investment tips haar same and
army 2017 person and twenty three so four
see Selva you can like this
from Vande Kendra this choc stock so
we are doing fish curry and also this thick 60 year old
Manish Kunjam you can see here the
2014 top has come so 8006 he made the middle of the
level of teaching which is the first plant lens
support of this, its first support has been broken
next support Sunday next again by
plastering those support Sunday we will
track it first next Monday when the
market is up then you will first see
if it takes support then you
can definitely try some quantity if for some
reason the teaching breaks then where can it go to take
support  It is very important to know
what can be done if the stock falls. It
can also be stressed from the stock. It is
very important to know where to take support
because it comes there. If it
falls even after taking crime rate support in the teacher, then you may have to take it down. So it is
very important to know. So
only the Sunday aspect which is level f-18
phase, I think if for some reason the fiber
comes in editing and gives support, a test
price goes, according to the current seniors, there is
development, then the container keeps falling, if the
teaching is broken continuously, then the fiber
can wait in the past if there is support around it, if
some contingencies will do bike, then the
person biker bike is not that big
brother, so those who have
not done it yet, are tracking it, if it
opens on Monday, there is some decline in it, then if the
equation for edge sports, then you could
definitely try it. So let's go to my
next Hindustan Unilever
Reference, the uncrowned king of this sector,
without Reference, no
refrigerator stock has become so
good in the morning.  It is a good stock, if you
take any item from your house, then the mixture which
we use in the house, there is some
product of another youth in it, a
little mixture will come to you, okay, so
according to the market subject you can see,
here its peel skip, its
marks question and he made it is
202, you
can see its 1575 bills, 2030 senior 3000
senior town planner RO electronic, which
is such a good stock, if you get it on corruption, then you
can submit it in the office by talking to the global, such
stock and you can estimate it in MS Word,
if I saw it behind the pistachio and C sector, if you
compare it with it, then
you can understand which batter it is, okay, so let's see it, you can
like it, so
its delivery and personal, I
saw here, ruling almost, it is giving
2014-part, he made 2178
12625, so see below  By installing it here, it was
against
Twenty20 and
from 76776 people deposited it in the box office,
similar chats, most of the people will
talk about this decision, today the bike is over, so
when it goes up on Monday, only then we will
see that you can like the sentence
and I will definitely give you its latest updates as soon as I
take you, Shilpa has to like that
when this stock is based on correction, right now
I have told its level that in 2050 some
quantity bike, if there is evidence, that stock, that
tap, then it saw the past chocolate at 1965, then the
next support which is formed,
2018 and always in the second grade, we will
not talk about it, we will see on Monday about 2016, whether it
comes here and takes support or not, then
give it time, after that you can bike it, there is
no need to form a military team,
so immediately let the teaching come a little, it
takes support here, you can definitely try it for a few hours,
next, if for some reason the 2016 rate
breaks even after taking support, then
you can change it or bike it
or else  They will get angry and while
telling them to take this below, they should
say dowry as per the current system, in the
coming apps, any pressure can
come in the market at a time, those are different things, but
your Joshi has made this mark on the edition
that this person can take support
and there he can destroy the next one, okay, so
definitely clear the playlist with this video, thank you.